Good morning.
I smashed the whites here yesterday.
I'm too hungry for egg pudding.
I'm going to order it online.
It's super tasty pudding!
You must try it!
Thank you very much!
Good morning.
In the fridge.
I forgot the juice of the swollen lemon.
I love it.
Wait, isn't this crazy? There's so much of it.
What's this?
Is that it? Is that the middle one?
I love it.
What's the green one?
Oh, something.
Ten minutes.
You can do it in 10 minutes.
It's like this.
What's that? It said 15 minutes.
Fifteen minutes.
I might have been working on it.
Yu-Yu or this way?
I might have done it.
Cameraman: This is sweet.
Cameraman: This is still, um...
It's really a chai chu...
What? Chai choux is good, but
It's not too sweet.
The food, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time...
Unforgettable, isn't it?
Dazzling, so bright, so shiny
I'm going to deliver it to the whole world, and say
Morning is coming, yay
Happy happy happy, happy rubble
Happy happy happy, happy rubble Happy happy happy rubble.
A little bit, I see.
Sweet smells, hoo hoo hoo
Happy happy happy, happy happy
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting all day.
Too cute.
Too cute. I'm waiting.
I've been waiting for you.
I've been waiting for you ever since you came.
He's coming.
He checks every few minutes.
You must really like him.
It turns out.
SUSU?
I found out his name.
SUSU.
SUSU
Oh no!
LOL!
One minute left?
Two more minutes.
Really, two more minutes.
But...
At least, I'm better than you.
Laugh.
LOL.
I kept saying, “Oh, what?” Like, “Oh, what?
But I've done it all.
You know.
I'm...
I feel pretty good.
Still within 50 minutes
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time for your basket of noodles!
It varies from shaggy to shaggy, though. Varies from shaggy to shaggy, though.
Well, well, well.
Thank you for watching.
Over there. Over there.
I've never had my face burned off.
Can we go?
You can do it.
Thank you very much.
What?
Good night.
It's done!
How do you eat it when it's done?
Soy sauce?
I'll tell you what, it looks good.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's good.
Cash match.
One, one, one.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
Oh, it's the last one on the plate.
Oh, chashu pork.
It's so good!
It took.
Bon appétit.
Have you eaten already?
Hey, I don't have a plate.
I'm glad. Let's eat.
Rock~. I'm going to rock from the outside.
What's that?
Strawberry cream.
Strawberry milk? Delicious cream.
I took a black sesame man, a small basket and a sandwich.
Thank you for the food.
Bon appétit.
Ah! Fresh chocolate! Ah! Fresh chocolates!
Can you grab a bag?
I'll have some!
The sandwich tasted buttery and super delicious!
What a surprise!
Super warm!
I've already taken your place!
Delicious steamed buns!
Bon appétit!
I'll have the calzanne soup.
I want some fresh chocolate.
You can eat four.
White chocolate, raw chocolate.
You can have four kinds.
Raw chocolate.
This is Oharu no ume.
I'm going to the last one.
Looks delicious.
This sandwich was delicious.
I want to ask Oharu if I can eat it last.
Looks delicious.
I recommend this sandwich for butter lovers.
It's buttery.
It's so buttery.
Was it money?
It's me.
You're full.
Okay, beer and rice done.
Bye-bye.
Okay, I'll have it with dark hiyorin.
Dark chocolate.
I'm gonna have some.
It tastes bitter.
Don't look at me, it's embarrassing.
You're so sweet to look at me.
I can do this on my own.
That's right.
Thank you for watching. Thank you for watching.
I'm going to sleep once more and would like to get it and go.
Bye-bye.
Squid and
kyunoponki
Bon appétit!
Very slowly!
I had it a while ago.
The inside is tender.
Bon appétit!
Hot!
Thank you for the food!
Accor and orb
Yum!
It was delicious!
That's great!
You know, I think it's the shoes.
I don't think they're compatible with the floor.
Next time.
Oh, I'll be here.
Good night.
Okay, I'll get ready then.
Ta-da!
Hiei's bangs.
Amazing.
Mr. Koizumisawa came to our conference.
Because our bangs were all too unruly yesterday
He came to ask about the key points of bangs.
I taught him about capes and he said he'd give it a try.
It looks like this.
I'm off now.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Good work.
Good work
Lots of pictureslots of photos!
We posted post insx and insta immediately after the show!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Next Episode Trailer
Next Trailer
Thank you for watching!
Hello hello hello to the new you, it doesn't matter what they say, let's attack harder and harder!
I believe that the most powerful live performance is the one with the six of us, the publicity staff, and everyone's voice.
That's why I want to come back to this big, big Saitama Super Arena with everyone.
It may be a big dream, but if we all give it our all and keep chasing our dreams, I'm sure it will come true.
Let's make such a big dream come true together and become the most powerful Tokimeki Advertising Department members!
Thank you for watching!
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turned color
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
It leads me to the future.
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
I can tell you the reason for my tears now... Whenever you're lost, just remember.
Even if it's raining, I'll smile, here I go, no matter how far I have to go.
Good-bye, goodbye, goodbye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye, good-bye
Rainbow pools, rainbow pianos, rainbow pianos, rainbow pianos.
Goodbye goodbye, I'm the one from yesterday, after the rain, the streets are sparkling, my heart is sunny
My heart is like a rainbow, my tears are making me wear a rainbow dress.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Thank you for watching!